A Finding Aid to the Donald Saff papers and Saff Tech Arts Records, circa 1710, 1800-2013 bulk 1965-2010, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Donald Saff Papers, circa 1710-2010; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 9.6 Linear feet Boxes 1-10, 33; 9.18 Gigabytes ER001-ER009
  - Writings, circa 1966-2010; 1.4; Archival Resource Key; 0.6 Linear feet Box 4; 0.019 Gigabytes ER003-ER004
    - Writings by Others, "Windows on Saff's World" (Unknown Author), circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Writings by Others, "Ask a Friend to Join You on Your Next Voyage" by Robert Gibbons, circa 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Exhibition Records, circa 1950-2010; 1.5; Archival Resource Key; 3.9 Linear feet Boxes 5-9; 9.18 Gigabytes ER005-ER009
    The exhibition subseries includes Saff's solo and group shows as an artist, as well as shows focusing on him as a fabricator and collaborator including the unrealized Joint Venture: Donald Saff and the Art of Collaboration, which was scheduled to open in Fall of 2009 at the Brooklyn Museum.
    - Donald Saff: Rememberances Getler/Pall/Saper (Feb. - Mar. 1984), circa 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Donald Saff: Sculpture Edison Community College (Mar.-Apr. 1988), circa 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Winged Metaphor: Sculpture and Prints by Donald Saff Barbara Gillman Gallery (1989), circa 1988-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Mixed Metaphors: Donald Saff 1956-1989 Tampa Museum of Art (Apr.-May 1989), circa 1988-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 35-38)
    - Donald Saff: Mixed Metaphors 1956-1991 Virginia Beach Center for the Arts(Sep.-Nov. 1991), circa 1988-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
    - Made in Florida University of South Florida (Mar. 1988-Jan. 1999), circa 1988-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 3-4)
    - Made in Florida Harn Museum of Art,U of Florida (Feb.-Apr. 1992), circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Poetics: Work by Donald Saff Brenau University (Feb.-Apr. 1997), circa 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
    - Joint Venture: Donald Saff and the Art of Collaboration Brooklyn Museum (Fall 2009:Unrealized), Archival Resource Key
      - Correspondence, Brooklyn Museum, circa 2002-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 8-10)
      - Correspondence, Emails, circa 2005-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Untitled Press (Robert Rauschenberg), circa 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Budget, circa 2007-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Expenses, circa 2007-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Expenses, Travel, circa 2006-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Brooklyn Museum Artwork Holdings, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Loan Forms, circa 2007-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Catalog, circa 2007-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Catalog Correspondence, Aquavella Gallery, circa 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Catalog Correspondence, Artists Rights Society, circa 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Catalog Correspondence, Publication Agreement, circa 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Catalog Correspondence, Prestel Publishing, circa 2009-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Catalog Correspondence, Caption Inquiries, circa 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Catalog Correspondence, Reproduction Permissions, circa 2007-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Catalog Correspondence, Reproduction Permissions (Saff Releases), circa 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - Catalog, Manuscript Drafts, circa 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 26-27)
      - Catalog, Manuscript Edits, Comments, circa 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Catalog, Essay Illustrations, circa 2007-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 29-31)
      - Catalog, Essay Illustrations, circa 2007-2010; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records; see ER005 and ER006. (Box 7, Folder 1-8)
      - Catalog, Saff Tech Arts, Digital Photographs, 2008; Archival Resource Key; 3.86 Gigabytes 364 computer files (Folder ER005)
      - Catalog, Saff Tech Arts, Digital Photographs, 2009; Archival Resource Key; 2.26 Gigabytes 187 computer files (Folder ER006)
      - Catalog, Illustrations, Slides and Notes from DJS, circa 1990s-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Catalog, Image Captions, circa 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Checklists, circa 2006-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 11-19)
      - Checklist (Lichtenstein Works and Texts), circa 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Checklist, Works with Credits and Location, circa 2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Checklist, Works with Credits and Location, circa 2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Interviews by Marilyn S. Kushner, circa 2004-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 2-4)
      - Research Material, Roy Lichtenstein Foundation Oral History Project, Avis Berman with Donald Saff (Mar. 17. 2009), Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Research Material, Jim Dine, circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Research Material, Roy Lichtenstein, circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Research Material, Robert Rauchenberg, circa 1989-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Research Material, James Rosenquist, circa 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Research Material, Associated Artists STA, circa 1990s-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10-12)
      - Research Material, Miscellaneous STA, circa 1990s-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13-14)
      - Research Material, Donald Saff Chronology, circa 1990s-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 15-16)
      - Research Material, Donald Saff Articles, circa 1950s-2000s; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records; see ER007. (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Donald Saff Talk at Academy of Art Museum Easton (Feb. 17, 2006), Digital Video Recording, Archival Resource Key; 2.77 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER007)
      - Research Material, Donald Saff Exhibitions, circa 1989-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Research Material, Donald Saff Quotations, circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Research Material, Donald Saff Interviews, circa 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records; see ER008. (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Donald Saff Interviews, Tampa (Oct. 2006), Digital Audio Recordings, Archival Resource Key; 0.264 Gigabytes Ten computer files (Folder ER008)
      - Research Material, Donald Saff Bibliography, circa 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 5-10)
      - Research Material, STA Chronology Artworks, circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Research Material, Miscellaneous, circa 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 12-13)
    - Miscellaneous Exhibition Documents, Donald Saff, circa 1979-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Exhibition Documents, Digital Documents, 2008-2009; Archival Resource Key; 0.016 Gigabytes Eighty-three computer files
  - Photographic Material, circa 1970-2002; 1.6; Archival Resource Key; 0.2 Linear feet Box 9
    Photographic material includes images of Donald Saff and associates, as well as his artwork.
    - Donald Saff, circa 1970s-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Deli Salicotto, circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Saff Artwork - Double Intaglios Photo Credit Geoffrey Clements, circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Saff Artwork, General, circa 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Corona del Coronero Graveyard, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Printed Material, circa 1800-2009; 1.7; Archival Resource Key; 0.8 Linear feet Boxes 9-10, 33
    Printed material subseries contains printed material related to Donald Saff's life and career before and followin Saff Tech Arts, focusing on him as an educator and artist and founder of Graphicstudio, and the legacy of the art collection Saff assembled.
    - Donald Saff Exhibition Announcements and Invitations, circa 1989-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Donald Saff Exhibition Catalogs, circa 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Donald Saff Clippings, circa 1966-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 22-23)
    - Donald Saff Clippings 1970s, circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Donald Saff Clippings 1980s, circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Donald Saff Clippings 1990s, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Donald Saff Oversize Clippings, circa 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Donald Saff, Saff Collection Miscellaneous, circa 1965-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 27-28)
    - University of South Florida (USF), Graphicstudio, circa 1973-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 29-30)
    - University of South Florida (USF), Graphicstudio Clippings, circa 1988-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Congressional Record (Mar. 3 1986) Graphicstudio, USF Commended, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - USF Graphic Impressions Spring, Fall 1997, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - University of South Florida (USF), Graphicstudio Miscellaneous, 1976-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Pyramid Arts, Ltd. Print Announcements, Various Artists, circa 1975-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Stanley T. Lewis, circa 1959-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Antique Mounted Prints, circa 1800s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Stamps, circa 1970s-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Printed Material, circa 1960s-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Oversize Printed Material, 1992, 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Artwork, circa 1970s-1990s; 1.8; Archival Resource Key; 0.1 Linear feet Box 33
    The artwork subseries includes various sketches and notes by Donald Saff, as well as a test print made for wither Saff or another artist.
    - Sketches and Notes, circa 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified Print Proof, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Saff Tech Arts Records, circa 1970-2013; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 22.2 Linear feet Boxes 10-32, 34; .640 Gigabytes ER010-ER011
  Saff Tech Arts (later Saff & Co.) records includes correspondence, founding documents including funding, fabrication and supplies information, artist files documenting working relationships ranging from potential collaboration, to long-term fabrication and representation, regular business relationships such as Knoedler & Co., and legal and insurance information including leases and worksite assessments, and printed material including clippings and subject files.
  The series is arranged as four subseries:
  2.1: Correspondence, circa 1988-2010
  2.2: Artist Files, circa 1970-2010
  2.3: Business Records, circa 1980-2011
  2.4: Printed Material, circa 1988-1999
  - Correspondence, circa 1988-2010; 2.1; Archival Resource Key; 2.7 Linear feet Boxes 10-12
    Saff Tech Arts Correspondence is a combination of incoming and outgoing and is arranged chronologically as well as alphabetically in select cases by correspondent. Correspondents are usually clients including collectors and galleries.
    - Chronological Correspondence, Archival Resource Key
      - Correspondence, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 10-11)
      - Correspondence, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 12-14)
      - Correspondence, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 15-16)
      - Correspondence, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 17-18)
      - Correspondence, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 20-23)
      - Correspondence, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 24-25)
      - Correspondence, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
      - Correspondence, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 3-5)
      - Correspondence (Ruth Saff, Outgoing), circa 1999-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 7-8)
      - Correspondence, circa 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, circa 2003-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Alphabetical Correspondence, Archival Resource Key
      - Evelyn Aimis Fine Art, circa 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Arnold Applebaum, 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Lucy Aptekar, 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Armistead and Capute Attorneys at Law, circa 1999, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Art in America, Various Artists, Ad Proofs, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Ahsley Aluminum, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - A, 1990, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Beckman-Parsons (Framing), circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Bernard Jacobson Gallery, circa 2002-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 19-21)
      - Janet Boris, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - B, circa 2003-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Corcoran Gallery of Art, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Mary Corlett (National Gallery of Art), circa 1999-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - CDS Fine Art Services, circa 1999-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - C, circa 1998-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Eckert Fine Arts, circa 2000-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Kenneth Endick, circa 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - E, circa 1991-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - F, circa 2003-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Gagosian Gallery, circa 2002-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Gemini GEL, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Arie Genger, circa 1991-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Bennet Grutman, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Guggenheim Museum, circa 1997-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - G, circa 1994-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - HW Gallery, circa 2001-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - H, circa 2006-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Alfred Kren, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - K, circa 1990-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Arnold Levine (Estate Valuation), circa 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - L, 1991, 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Roger Mandle (RISD), circa 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - M, circa 2002-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - N, circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - P, circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - R&A Cycles, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 27)
      - R, 1996, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 28)
      - Ron Saff, circa 2002-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 29)
      - Sash Spencer, circa 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 30)
      - Donald Sultan, circa 1991-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 31)
      - S, circa 2005-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 32)
      - T, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 33)
      - U, circa 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 34)
      - V, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 35)
      - Sigmund Wegner (Wegner Gallery), circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 36)
      - Bjorn Wetterling, circa 1988-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 37)
      - Winsor Porcelain (Al Winsor), circa 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 38)
      - W, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 39)
      - Potential Backers, circa 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 40)
      - STA Artist Addresses, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 41)
      - Potential STA Artists, circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Artist Files, circa 1970-2010; 2.2; Archival Resource Key; 15.2 Linear feet Boxes 12-27, 33; 0.64 Gigabytes ER010-ER011
    Artist files document a range of interest and working relationships ranging from potential collaboration, to long-term fabrication partnerships including representation. Regular collaborators included Nancy Graves, Robert Rauschenberg, Roy Lichtenstein, James Turrell, and James Rosenquist. Materials include printed material, fabrication information, sales and consignments, exhibition planning, shipping documents, and damage and restoration documentation.
    - Richard Artschwager, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Sandro Chia, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Christo & Jeanne Claude, circa 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Chuck Close, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Jim Dine, circa 1976-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 47-48)
    - Eric Fischl, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Helen Frankenthaler, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Frank Gehry, circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - April Gornick, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Nancy Graves, Archival Resource Key
      - Correspondence, circa 1990-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 53-54)
      - Correspondence, Nancy Graves Foundation, circa 1999-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 55)
      - Correspondence, Hecht & Co., circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 56)
      - Correspondence, K&B Incorporated, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 57)
      - Correspondence, Learning Designs, Inc., circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 58)
      - Correspondence, Reproduction Permissions, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
      - Conservation, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Consignment, Knoedler & Co., circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Exhibition, STA at Knoedler & Co. (Mar.-Apr. 1992), circa 1991-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Exhibition, Walla Walla Foundry (Jan.-Feb. 1993), circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Exhibition, U. of Maryland BC Fine Arts Gallery (Feb.-Mar. 1993), circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Exhibition, Meredith Long & Co. (Mar. 1994), circa 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Bones, Gnomons, and Longitude Series, Archival Resource Key
        - General, circa 1992-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 9-10)
        - Corrspondence, Irving Galleries, circa 1993-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 11)
        - Series Aggrement, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 12)
        - Exhibition, Locks Gallery (Korea, Unrealized) (Fall 1992), circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 13)
        - Exhibition, Knoedler & Co. (Apr.-May 1993), circa 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 14)
        - Inventory, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 15)
        - Invoices, circa 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Timepieces, Exhibition, Brenau University Galleries (Jan.-Mar. 1995), circa 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Timepieces, Exhibition, Lafayette Williams Center for the Arts (Sep.-Oct. 2001), circa 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Unending Revolution of Venus, Plants and Pendulum #310, Archival Resource Key
        - General, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 19)
        - Walla Walla Foundry (Nov. 2011) A-D Sculptures, circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 20)
        - Contract, Learning Designs, Hyperion Books, circa 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 21)
        - Billing, circa 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Small Sculptures with Walla Walla Foundry #320, Archival Resource Key
        - General, circa 1992-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 23)
        - Seven Sculptures and Specifications to Finish, circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 24)
        - Clock Assembly Instructions, circa 1991-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 25)
        - Billing, circa 1991-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 26-27)
      - Joint Venture: Project #310, #320 Agreement, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - Joint Venture Billing, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - Tango Series with Deli Salicotto, Iris Editions, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 30)
      - Nancy Graves Signatures, circa 1992-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 31)
      - Inventory (1 and 2 of 3), circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 32-33)
      - Inventory (3 of 3), circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - STA Inventory, circa 1992-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Invoices, circa 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Material Worksheets, Fabrication Purchases, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Signed Releases, circa 1990-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Printed Material, Announcements, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Printed Material, STA at Knoedler Exhibition Announcement Art in America(Mar. 1992), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Printed Material, STA Advertisement, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Printed Material, Clippings, circa 1986-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Printed Material, Miscellaneous, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Writings, Notes, circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 11-12)
      - Writings, Memorial and Eulogy by Donald Saff, circa 1995-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 13-14)
      - Nancy Graves Visits to STA, circa 1991-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Howard Hodgkin, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Jasper Johns, circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Jeff Koons, circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Roy Lichtenstein, Archival Resource Key
      - Correspondence (General), circa 1989-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, Estate and Foundation, circa 1997-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 20)